Guide to the Van Ness-Philip Family Papers 1711-1963 (bulk 1711-1945) MS 653
New-York Historical Society
- Series VII: John Van Ness Philip (d. 1949)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Printed material, undated (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Printed material, undated (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper clippings, undated (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Law school notes (1), circa 1890 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Law school notes (2), circa 1891 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Law school notes (3), undated (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Law school notes (4), undated (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - White House invitations: Mr. and Mrs. Philip, 1894-1945 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - White House invitation, Congress invitations, Inaugurals: 1933, 1937, 1945, 1933-1964 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Printed invitations: wedding, social, official events, undated (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Invitations and printed cards, undated (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Invitations and printed cards, undated (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Invitations and printed cards, undated (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Invitations and printed cards, undated (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Pocket journal, 1887-1889 (Box 59, Folder unknown container)
  - Military calculations log, 1918 (Box 59, Folder unknown container)
  - Spanish phrase book, undated (Box 59, Folder unknown container)
  - Riggs and Co. account book, 1891-1893 (Box 59, Folder unknown container)
  - Visiting list, undated (Box 59, Folder unknown container)
  - Log, circa 1897-1898 (Box 59, Folder unknown container)
  - Field message book, U. S. Army, 1918 (Box 59, Folder unknown container)
  - Composition book (1), undated (Box 59, Folder unknown container)
  - Composition book (2), undated (Box 59, Folder unknown container)
  - Military message log book, 1918 (Box 59, Folder unknown container)
  - Notebook of John Van Ness Philip (with recipes) (Box 59, Folder unknown container)
  - "Philip Estate" monthly account with John Van Ness Philip, 1892-1893 (Box 59, Folder unknown container)
  - Book of letters, circa 1897-1898 (Box 59, Folder unknown container)
  - Legal papers (unsorted), circa 1897-1908 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Legal papers (unsorted), circa 1857-1882 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Legal papers (unsorted), circa 1890-1897 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Legal papers (unsorted), circa 1891-1893 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Legal papers (unsorted), circa 1891-1897 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Legal papers (unsorted), circa 1882-1901 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Legal papers (unsorted), circa 1889-1897 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Legal papers (unsorted), circa 1896-1905 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Legal papers (unsorted), circa 1863-1880 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Legal papers (unsorted), circa 1896-1900 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Legal papers (unsorted), circa 1864-1905 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Legal papers (unsorted), circa 1880-1902 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Legal papers (unsorted), circa 1866-1876 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Legal papers (unsorted), circa 1872-1892 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Legal papers (unsorted), circa 1848-1876 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Legal papers (unsorted), circa 1872-1892 (Box 63, Folder 4)
- Series VIII: Herman Hoffman Philip
  This series covers Herman Hoffman Philip, circa 1870-1950, covering his years at Cambridge University, travels in the far West, service with the Rough Riders on San Juan Hill, travels in Europe, years in the diplomatic service in the Mid-East, Africa, Scandinavia, and South America, and correspondence and publications after his retirement.
  - Correspondence, circa 1870-1889 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, undated, 1890-1897 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, undated, 1898 Jan.-1898 Jul. (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1898 Aug.-1898 Dec. (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1899 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1900 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, circa 1900-1910 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, undated, 1904-1915 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Notes on condition of prisoners: Afion Kara Hissar, 1915 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - San Stefano and Gallipoli hostages, 1915 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Syrian relief, 1916-1917 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Cairo, 1917 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1916-1919 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence (Columbia), 1920-1924 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1925-1929 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1930-1936 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Chile, 1936-1937 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1937-1939 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1940-1945 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1946-1950 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Knight v. Knight correspondence, 1940-1942 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Letters on death of H. Hoffman Philip, 1951-1952 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Misc. correspondence, undated (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Special correspondence (1), 1901-1928 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Special correspondence (2), 1930-1936 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Special correspondence (3), 1937-1949 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - White House invitations: Coolidge, Hoover, Rosevelt, 1928-1937 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Photographs, 1935, undated (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Passport, traveling papers, 1914-1928 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Speeches, drafts, 1902-1929 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Drafts of speeches, articles, 1914-1932 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous (1), 1877-1951 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous (2), 1893-1927 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous (3), 1898-1910 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous (4), 1898-1938 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Newsclippings: career, 1898-1937 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - "Tangier Holiday" illustrations, 1945 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Photographs, Illustrations, 1909-1912, undated (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Photographs, Illustrations, 1947-1948 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Writings (1), undated (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Writings (2), 1880, 1945 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Writings (3), 1943-1945, undated (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Address book, circa 1910 (Box 68, Folder unknown container)
  - Notepad, undated (Box 68, Folder unknown container)
  - Identity card, 1922 (Box 68, Folder unknown container)
  - Notebook, circa 1908 (Box 68, Folder unknown container)
  - Daylogue, 1919-1922 (Box 68, Folder unknown container)
  - Notebook, circa 1946 (Box 68, Folder unknown container)
  - Daybook: Abyssinia, 1909-1910 (Box 68, Folder unknown container)
  - Adresses [sic], circa 1917-1925 (Box 68, Folder unknown container)
  - Address book/journal, circa 1915 (Box 68, Folder unknown container)
  - Journal, 1904 (Box 68, Folder unknown container)
  - Journal, 1909-1919 (Box 68, Folder unknown container)
  - Journal, 1897-1898 (Box 68, Folder unknown container)
  - Scrap book of newspaper clippings concerning the Spanish-American War, 1898 (Box 68, Folder unknown container)
- Series IX: Philip Family
  The Philip Family papers contains business and personal correspondence as well as bills and receipts and schoolwork. Items of note are letters of Theodore Roosevelt, Franklin D., and Eleanor Roosevelt. Also included are writings, speeches, illustrations and volumes.
  - Gaston Philip:: Bills and receipts, undated, 1895-1897 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Gaston Philip: Correspondence and photographs, flag from U.S. Geological Survey, 1893-1900 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Bessie Philip: Correspondence upon death of mother (1), 1896 Oct.-1896 Nov. (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Bessie Philip: Correspondence upon death of mother (2), 1896 Oct.-1896 Nov. (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Bessie Philip: Correspondence, undated, 1890-1899 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Catherine Philip: Correspondence, undated, 1838-1847 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Catherine Philip: Correspondence, 1853-1863 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Martin Hoffman Philip: school compositions, undated, 1839-1841 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Martin Hoffman Philip: correspondence, invitations, undated, 1846-1878 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Compilation of letters to Eliza W. Philip, circa 1889-1891 (Box 70, Folder unknown container)
  - Journal and correspondence of Eliza Worthington, circa 1853-1863 (Box 70, Folder unknown container)
  - Servants account book, circa 1881-1887 (Box 70, Folder unknown container)
  - Account book of W. H. Philip, 1879 (Box 70, Folder unknown container)
  - Account book of Eliza W. Philip, 1889-1893 (Box 70, Folder unknown container)
  - Diary of Catherine Dorn Philip, Talavera, 1860-1863 (Box 70, Folder unknown container)
  - Notebook of novels read, undated (Box 70, Folder unknown container)
  - File Index - J. Van Ness Philip no. I, undated (Box 70, Folder unknown container)
  - File Index - J. Van Ness Philip no. II, undated (Box 70, Folder unknown container)
  - Indentures, will, 1795-1809 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: indentures, undated, 1810-1819 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: indentures, undated, 1820-1824 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: indentures, 1825-1829 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Wills and estate (Henry G.), business correspondence, 1830 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, business correspondence, 1831-1832 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Business correspondence, 1833 Jan.-1833 Aug. (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Business correspondence, 1833 Sep.-1833 Dec. (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Business correspondence, 1834 Jan.-1834 Apr. (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Business correspondence, 1834 May-1834 Nov. (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Legal papers between James Philip and J. Rutsen Van Renssalaer, 1806-1834 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Business correspondence, 1835 Jan.-1835 May (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Business correspondence, 1835 Jun.-1835 Oct. (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Business correspondence, 1837-1838 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Business correspondence, 1839 Jan.-1839 Jun. (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Business correspondence, 1839 Jul.-1839 Nov. (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Business correspondence, 1842 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Business correspondence, 1843-1844 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Business correspondence, 1845 Jan.-1845 Jun. (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Business correspondence, 1845 Jul.-1845 Dec. (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Business correspondence, 1847 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Business correspondence, 1848 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Business correspondence, 1849 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Business correspondence, 1850-1851 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Bills and receipts, undated, 1824-1825 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Bills and receipts, 1826 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Bills and receipts, 1827 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Bills and receipts, 1828 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Bills and receipts, 1829 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Bills and receipts, 1829 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Bills and receipts, 1830 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Bills and receipts, 1830 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Bills and receipts, 1831 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Bills and receipts, 1831 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Bills and receipts, 1832 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Bills and receipts, 1832 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Bills and receipts, 1833 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Bills and receipts, 1833 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Bills and receipts, 1834-1839 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Bills and receipts, 1840-1842 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Bills and receipts, 1843 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Bills and receipts, 1844 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Bills and receipts, 1845 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Bills and receipts, 1850-1854 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Bills and receipts, 1860-1865 (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Bills and receipts, 1870-1879 (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Bills and receipts, 1880-1886 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Bills and receipts, 1892-1898 (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Bills and receipts, undated (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Bills and receipts, 1820-1840's (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Bills and receipts, circa 1820-1850 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Bills and receipts, undated (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Bills and receipts, undated (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Bills and receipts, undated (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Bills and receipts, undated (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, clippings and receipts, late 1800's (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Bills and receipts, 1890's (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Bound volume, The Book of Common Prayer, 1849 (Box 78, Folder unknown container)
  - Bound volume, Hymns, Ancient and Modern, 1884 (Box 78, Folder unknown container)
  - Bound volume, The Churchman's Altar Manual and Guide to the Holy Communion, 1880 (Box 78, Folder unknown container)
  - Bound volume, The Book of the Common Prayer, 1846 (Box 78, Folder unknown container)
  - Bound volume, Psalms in Metre, 1833 (Box 78, Folder unknown container)
  - Cards, circa 1870-1890 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Bills, receipts and correspondence (W.H. Philip), circa 1870-1890 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Calling cards, envelopes and bills, circa 1886-1888 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Report cards, correspondence, book illustrations, calling cards, receipts, circa 1885-1890 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Calling cards, correspondence, bills, history notes, menu, undated (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Calling cards, invitations, correspondence, clippings, receipts, circa 1850-1890 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Calling cards, correspondence, bills, receipts, circa 1877-1888 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Calling cards, correspondence, bills and receipts, circa 1875-1885 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Calling cards, correspondence, clippings, bills and receipts, circa 1878-1899 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - School reports, invitations, clippings, correspondence, certificates, bills, circa 1860-1896 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, circa 1840-1863 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Religious newsclippings, undated (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Invitations, circa 1896-1901 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Printed articles and speeches, circa 1851-1871 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Printed matter on free trade, circa 1870 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Printed school material, circa 1820-1892 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Printed ephemera material and music score, circa 1846-1893 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Bond Certificates, Columbia Bank notes, circa 1860-1873 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Clipping, account of the Spanish-American War, El Banco de Columbia note, Treaty, U.S. and Morocco, 1837, undated (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Printed material, Map of Washington D.C., the Anti-Rent war, advertisements, 1879, undated (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Family photographs, undated (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Printed material, Constitution and By-Laws of the Metropolitan Club, 1873 (Box 81, Folder unknown container)
  - Printed material, Instructions on the Defensive Actions of Large Units in Battle, 1918 Mar. (Box 81, Folder unknown container)
  - Printed material, Liason For All Arms, 1918 June (Box 81, Folder unknown container)
  - Printed material, Artillery Notes, 1917 (Box 81, Folder unknown container)
  - Printed material, Ugo Bassi's Sermon in the Hospital, 1888 (Box 81, Folder unknown container)
  - Printed material, Val D'Arno, 1884 (Box 81, Folder unknown container)
  - Printed material, Der Spanische Student, undated (Box 81, Folder unknown container)
  - Bound volume, Golden Thoughts from the Imitation of Christ, undated (Box 81, Folder unknown container)
  - Bound volume, Primary Arithmetic, 1875 (Box 81, Folder unknown container)
  - Bound volume, The Episcopal Manual, 1822 (Box 81, Folder unknown container)
  - Printed material, The South African Crisis, 1900 (Box 81, Folder unknown container)
  - Printed material, Instructions for the Offensive Combat of Small Units, 1918 (Box 81, Folder unknown container)
  - Bound volume, The Epistle of Paul the Apostle to the Galatians, undated (Box 81, Folder unknown container)
  - Bound volume, The Acts of the Apostles, undated (Box 81, Folder unknown container)
  - Printed material, Constitution and By-Laws of the Maryland Historical Society, 1867 (Box 81, Folder unknown container)
  - Printed material, Trench Accessories, 4th Division (Regular), undated (Box 81, Folder unknown container)
  - Bound volume, The Changed Cross and Other Religious Poems, 1872 (Box 81, Folder unknown container)
  - Printed material, Golden Thoughts from the Imitation of Christ, undated (Box 81, Folder unknown container)
  - Printed material, The Man Term Festivities, 1894 (Box 81, Folder unknown container)
  - Printed material, National Constitution of the Society of the Colonial Dames of America, undated (Box 81, Folder unknown container)
  - Printed material, Porzellan-Fabrik von Fischer & Mieg, 1807 (Box 81, Folder unknown container)
  - Printed material, Running Rules of the National Beagle Club of America, 1894 (Box 81, Folder unknown container)
  - Printed material, U.P.C. Rules, Regulations, Etc., 1892 (Box 81, Folder unknown container)
  - Printed material, The German Conquest of England in 1875 and Battle of Dorking, undated (Box 81, Folder unknown container)
  - Printed material, Instruction on the Offensive Action of Large Units in Battle, 1918 (Box 81, Folder unknown container)
  - Printed sermon, Food and Morals, 1888 (Box 81, Folder unknown container)
  - Printed material, The Training and Employment of Divisions, 1918 (Box 81, Folder unknown container)
  - Playbill, L'Aiglon (featuring Sarah Bernhardt), 1900 (Box 81, Folder unknown container)
  - Printed material, Constitution and By-Laws of the Society of the Army of Santiago de Cuba, 1900 (Box 81, Folder unknown container)
  - Printed material, Convention between the United States and Other American Republics: Inter-American Conciliation, 1929 (Box 81, Folder unknown container)
  - Printed material, Treaty between the United States and Other American Republics: To Avoid or Prevent Conflicts between the American States, 1927 (Box 81, Folder unknown container)
  - Printed material, Department of State Telephone Directory, Republic 5600, 1947 Dec. (Box 81, Folder unknown container)
  - Printed material, The Hoffman Philip Abyssinian Ethnological Collection, 1911 (Box 81, Folder unknown container)
  - Periodical, The Philadelphian, 1887 (Box 81, Folder unknown container)
  - Periodical, The Yale Review, 1944 (Box 81, Folder unknown container)
  - Periodical, The Atlantic Monthly, undated (Box 81, Folder unknown container)
  - Printed material, The Hoffman Philip Abyssinian Ethnological Collection, 1911 (Box 81, Folder unknown container)
  - Printed material, A Residence in France; With an Excursion Up the Rhine, and a Second Visit to Switzerland by James Fenimore Cooper, 1836 (Box 81, Folder unknown container)
  - Periodical, Magazine of American History, 1885 (Box 81, Folder unknown container)
  - Printed material, Two New African Ratels, 1910 (Box 81, Folder unknown container)
  - Periodical, Harper's New Monthly Magazine, 1875 Feb. (Box 81, Folder unknown container)
- Series X. Worthington Family
  This series contains material relating to the Worthington family, ca. 1817-1900, including correspondence, 1817-21, between Midshipman Thomas B. Worthington and his physician father Charles Worthington; correspondence and papers of lawyer William M. Worthington; correspondence, ca. 1830's-1875, of John G. Worthington, covering his early law practice in Cincinnati, Ohio, and later years in Washington, D.C. as well as family correspondence, ca. 1850's-1900.
  - Letters to John G. Worthington from William M. Worthington, 1822-1841 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Letters to John G. Worthington from Charles Worthington, 1826-1835 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Letters to John G. Worthington from brother N.W. Worthington and sister Catherine Pearson, 1822-1846 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence to John G. Worthington re: Business, legal matters, receipts, 1825-1843 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Letters from Thomas B. Worthington to Dr. Charles Worthington (father), 1817-1821 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence to William M. Worthington, 1820-1824 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence to William M. Worthington from Henry Clay, 1820 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Deed (land) to William M. Worthington, 1817-1818 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Elizabeth Worthington papers, undated (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Eliza (Lilah) Worthington-Philip (married to William H. Philip) papers, 1856-1866 (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Letters to Charles Worthington, 1875-1898 (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Worthington family correspondence, undated (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Legal correspondence and papers, undated (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous receipts, 1842-1843 (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, circa 1820 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, cicra 1830 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, circa 1840 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence to and from Eliza (Lila) Worthington, circa 1840-1850 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1853-1854, 1856-1859 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1855 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, circa 1860 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence from Mrs. John G. Worthington to Lilah Worthington Philip, circa 1860 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence to Mrs. John G. Worthington, 1870-1878 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence to Mrs. John G. Worthington, 1879 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, circa 1870 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, circa 1870 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, circa 1870 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, circa 1870 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, undated, circa 1880 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1880 Jan.-Aug. (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1880 Sept.-Dec. (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1881 Jan.-June (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1881 July-Dec. (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1882 Jan.-Aug. (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1882 Sept.-Dec. (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1883 Jan.-June (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1883 July (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1883 Aug.-Dec. (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1884 Jan.-Aug. (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1884 Sept.-Dec. (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1885 Jan.-June (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1885 July-Dec. (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1886 (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1887-1888 (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, clippings, photo, undated (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Receipts, newspaper clippings, travel brochures, cards, undated (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Calling cards and invitations, undated (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Photos, undated (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence between John G. Worthington and wife, 1869-1875 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence to John G. Worthington from son Charles, 1870-1874 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence between John G. Worthington and other family, 1859-1871 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - John G. Worthington, business correspondence, 1871-1872 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - John G. Worthington, business correspondence, 1873 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Letter to Mrs. John G. Worthington from daughter Eliza, undated, 1875-1877 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Letters to Mrs. John G. Worthington from daughter Eliza, 1878 (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Letters to Mrs. John G. Worthington from daughter Eliza, 1880-1885 (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Mrs. John G. Worthington, letter from daughter Rebecca, letter from Charles to wife Rebecca, 1880-1881 (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Mrs. John G. Worthington, other family correspondence, 1876-1888 (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - Mrs. John G. Worthington, correspondence from grandchildren, undated, 1873-1881 (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - Mrs. John G. Worthington, telegrams, letter regarding death of Eliza's husband, 1881 (Box 87, Folder 12)
  - Bills and receipts, circa 1837-1874 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Bills and receipts, circa 1864-1873 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Bound journal, Stories from the German, Translated for Eliza, 1875 (Box 89, Folder unknown container)
  - Journal of dried flowers, undated (Box 89, Folder unknown container)
  - Travel journal, Mr. John G. Worthington, Europe, 1854 (Box 89, Folder unknown container)
  - Account book, Europe, 1855-1857 (Box 89, Folder unknown container)
  - Journal of poetry, 1824 (Box 89, Folder unknown container)
  - Scrapbook of clippings and poetry, undated (Box 89, Folder unknown container)